I know just how to whisper
我明白如何耳语
And I know just how to cry
也明白如何哭喊
I know just where to find the answers, and I know just how to lie
我知道哪里可以找到答案  也知道如何去说谎
I know just how to fake it
我知道如何捏造事实
And I know just how to scheme
也知道如何策划阴谋
I know just when to face the truth, and then I know just when to dream
我知道何时该面对真相  也知道何时该去做梦
And I know just where to touch you,
我知道如何让你感动
And I know just what to prove
也知道该去证明
I know when to pull you closer
我知道何时该将你拉近一些
And I know when to let you loose
也知道何时该放手
And I know the night is fading
我知道夜晚即将结束
And I know the time's gonna fly
知道时间正在飞逝
And I'm never gonna tell you everything, I've gotta tell you. But I know I've gotta give it a try
而我绝不会告诉你任何必须告诉你的事  但我知道该试试看
And I know the roads to riches
我知道致富之道
And I know the ways to fame
也知道成名的路
I know all the rules and then I know how to break'em. And I always know the name of the game
我知道所有的游戏规则 也知道如何打破它们  我总是知道游戏的名称
But I don't know how to leave you
但我不知道如何离开你
And I'll never let you fall
我永远不会让你失望
And I don't know how you do it
我不明白你是怎么做到的
Making love out of nothing at all
凭空生爱
Out of nothing at all